So like you leave the room and just like your swimsuit and that's it, which as I said, like, you know, no phone, it was just great.
So I actually ended up losing 4 pounds from carrying the like four person like tube up like the 100 flights of stairs like three times in a row and then all the double s and then all the singles and then carrying for my son and then carrying my son, carrying my daughter. And so yeah, I lost 4 pounds on vacation.
Yeah.
Chu.
It's done.
And all the cold water, yeah.
Yeah.
All right.
John, do you know if we're getting Angie or Marty from our side over here today?
You know, I'm not sure about Martin. I didn't hear. I think Angie is perhaps going to pop in for a little bit, but, you know, I think we've got the core crew here, you know, Matt, Eric on your side and Rob and David, you guys, you know, really looking for that. And speaking of which, there she is.
Good.
There we go.
Just stop them.
I guess.
Angie, how are you?
Hey, Angie.
Good, good. How about yourself?
I know, doing well.
Set up for the kickoff.
Oh, there we go. Look at this. We're coming in force now.
Mhm.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hai.
We're officially outnumbered. How are you, Marty?
How's everybody doing?
What's going on? How are you?
Living the dream.
All right.
Actually working feverishly on a sidebar, installing some crap that David and Rob gave me. So.
I'm sorry.
It will change everything about how you work, Marty. You just got to roll with it.
Well, it's funny because I already have a heavily stylized chief of staff on the co-work side. So mine's a little more complicated because I'm munging the two together. So I'm having Claude kind of figure out what to keep from mine and what to incorporate from yours.
Yeah.
without tearing the whole thing apart because I already have a bit of a working thing.
Nice, nice.
We'll see. We're getting there.
Awesome.
Well, maybe as a side note, as we go through here, that's something cool we can share with Matt and Eric as we go to like.
Yeah, this is a kudos to Rob. Like Rob put together just this amazing framework for how to leverage all the AI stuff. I mean, obviously saw the magic show before, but there's like other stuff behind that. That's really cool.
Prem.
All right. I shared out a link in chat. This is the same Lucid board we were on before. I'm going to pull it up.
You're all welcome to jump in.
I'm sorry, you said you put that the link in the chat?
Yeah, it's in chat. It's the first thing in chat.
Gotcha.
Right, this is the same.
And then to orient you, yeah, I'm going to zoom out really quick. So we have a few sections. This left section is what we worked on last time. Up to the top right is a bunch of design stuff. I think Rob showcased when we were doing the.
the app sort of design work that we're doing earlier or when we're getting ready for demo and all that kind of stuff. So all of those that is there as an artifact. And then this bottom right section is today.
So what we're trying to do here, hopefully, this lands, is keep all the information in one place where we all have access to it. So anytime we do any design work or we have key discussions or just decisions, it's just nice to have one shared board. If we decide we don't want to do that and lose it later, that's fine, but.
You know, the goal is just everybody can see everything and we can always access the information together.
Cool. All right. Well, let's jump in and get started.
This agreements tracker to the left here is just things that we want to capture in our discussion today. I'm going to sort of skip past that and come back to it later. But we just want to make sure we go through a few things. We want to check in on where you are, check in on our understanding.
based on all the discussions that have happened since we last did that workshop.
Rob is going to walk us through sort of where we are today and get your perspective on where the app is and what you want based on that, you know, everything that's happened because it's been a few weeks. And then at the end here, we'll get into the next steps. What does the next two weeks look like? Action items.
wrangling our calendars as a group to make sure we have all the right meetings and stuff together so that we are working effectively. So that's the plan.
And let me know if there's anything you want to steer in a direction. Happy to do that.
Good.
Okay, so first piece is on our side. We have aligned A-team and we had an internal sort of kickoff sync yesterday to get everybody up to speed. So Rob is going to be directly on the team. We wanted to make sure that he...
was on this. He's going to have the role of engagement lead, but also like ensuring our team is like wielding all the tools and stuff that he was doing to make sure that we're doing this in the right way. We want him to stay as connected and involved as impossible. Because we all love Rob. So.
Shout out to you, Rob.
Next piece of that is the team is largely in India. So as we wrangle calendars together, Rob and myself will be sort of your US counterparts for discussions and things you need to do. We're going to set a cadence so where we can have stand-ups and
align some overlaps. Our India team is very used to working with us in this way. Generally, they're available for mornings, US time, but we can wrangle what we want out of that. But if there isn't enough overlap, Rob and I will make sure that we fill the gap and make sure that that stuff comes together. So we don't want that to be.
a perceived loss on your part, like we want to make sure we have high connectivity, where the right conversations are happening, all of that kind of stuff. So we have Vikas, he's the, he's going to be an AWS architect and engineering lead on the NDS side. We also have Nitish who is on the back end.
We have an iOS specific developer. So this is like a first point of question for you is given the shortened timeframe and the budget that we're working with, we want to focus on a single platform. Our assumption is right now that that should be iOS. If you want that to be Android, like let us know now and we can quick pivot.
and make sure that we have the right person for that.
I would assume iOS is probably the best way forward, correct? I mean, in your experience.
Um...
I think so. I mean, it it's um...
We talked about this last time. So it's a longer tail through the App Store. So if you're trying to get something in people's hands quicker, Android is probably a cleaner path and we can pass the APKs around. I don't know that it necessarily matters. It sort of matters what devices you all have.
Yap.
so you can look and try it and make sure that it's real and you're not just working with a web view. Like that, that I think is the key thing, because you know, what's the experience that we have? If your team is mixed on what devices you have, you know, we can navigate that. I think it's okay, but we want to sort of pick the thing that is the most pervasive.
for the Leadership team.
Yap, that's why I think most of the teams on iOS all buy an iPhone on the company card.
Excellent, OK.
I.
iOS is nice and fluid. What it does mean in here as well is that everybody on the team from a development standpoint needs to be running on a Mac. So Rob and I are, a couple of the others are, the AWS team members, we're issuing them on Mac right now on our side.
So they'll get that Friday is the plan and be up and running. So it just means, you know, two days of planning work and not necessarily iOS work for those team members until they're onboarded.
Yap.
OK, so.
On the SOW, what we've aligned on is an eight-week phase because of what I just mentioned.
on issuing devices and making sure that they actually have physical hardware. We want that to kick off on Monday. So the clock timer to start on a day for them so that everybody's up and that also gives us some onboarding time for them. So you're not basically paying for internal onboarding. We in terms of like overall capacity.
of the team and what we have from time and budget. We have about a third roughly of the original scope we talked about. So we need to have some discussions following this around how do we want to best maximize that time and what do we think we can fit and what are your priorities. So that's like a first step conversation we need to get.
Rolling right away.
I don't see that as a barrier to anything. We just need to be strategic with the time.
Also, we're assuming that we're running on Bedrock due to the Amazon agreement and what they're funding, and that we're going to go through everything via Claude through that path. We still want to validate a few things on that, but that's our sort of going in assumption at the moment.
Cook.
And then this, what does success look like? Like for us when we're thinking about this, we really want to focus having a working product in your hands at all times and just moving that ball forward as fast as we can. So from how we work,
perspective. We want to constantly demo to you at a regular cadence, have these handoffs and they are up and running and you can play with it. And then, you know, if anything happens, we stop or we want to, you know, change scope at any time. You always have a working product basically in your hands. So we want to focus that as like a team goal.
to make sure we're doing that effectively.
And then just proving that velocity, like we want to continue to bring our velocity and cadence up as a team with those handoffs to you as fast as we can throughout the engagement.
Um, okay, so...
Quick check in on your side. You know, one, does all that make sense? Is any of that contentious or do you want to edit it? And then you can see I created some initial cards here for discussion. I'm assuming, Eric, you're our main point of contact, basically product owner that our team is going to work with. Is that still a fair assumption?
Yes.
And then the other like call out here, I think this is in the SOW2 as we want to have a very tight.
communication loop on any decisions. So, you know, we stamp two days on here, but the end point is not to be two days. It's just that we're communicating effectively as fast as we can because we don't want the team to start working and going sideways one direction on assumptions, that kind of thing.
Agreed. And I think the only person I would even be bouncing this off of would be Matt, who I'm in constant contact with. So decisions could come very quickly.
Okay, great.
Okay, so has there been any decision since we've talked last on or promises that you've made on getting a beta out or, you know, is there investors you need to get this thing in the hands of? Anything that we need to know about?
I don't think there's anybody we need to necessarily get in the hands of. I think, you know, the North Star at this point is still Reinvent. So I think we are all aligned around that date and having, you know, having a launch in some capacity at Reinvent. So I'm actually talking to Ellen tomorrow. Marty, I'm going to sync myself, yourself.
Angie and Ellen together on Friday. But I think it's doable, you know, based on based on the timeline. The other thing to share with you guys is.
Well, maybe I'm getting ahead of myself. Let me just see.
Yeah, I think, you know, we took Rob's existing product and I probably have shown it to, I've shown it to all of our investors. Our board members have seen it. We've showed it to our advisory group. So we've got a lot of great feedback. And I think we've got a really, really clear vision for
what the product is, the why behind it, and really how we need to position it, especially during this MVP. So I think we've got a lot of clarity. We're very aligned internally. And I think because Rob, what Rob shared with us, just it probably had a lot more than people were expecting.
It was really, that was really beneficial for us. So I'll kind of pause there. I see your note about the other thing that we'll talk about real quick is we did have, we did have a couple meetings with Mission. And after talking to Mission and getting kind of a second scope of work from those guys,
What we decided to do was any of the artifact is obviously going to be a, it's going to be an essential piece of this product. We decided that we were better working with Bounteous on that. So not trying to split up the work and have two dev teams and sharing insights. So
And that was really a call, that call was really made in partnership with James, you know, who's our AWS account rep. I mean, James said, these guys are building this MVP, you know, let's see if we can support them, meaning AWS, to get ourselves, you know, in a healthier spot with the artifacts. So we kind of shared with Mission that for the time being, you know, we'll keep the door open, but.
you know, we're going to kind of charge you guys with that. And then I think we've got just a ton of feedback on the product, which is probably, you know, what we need to download on you guys. But other than that, yeah, the timeline for us from an investor perspective, we've got some investor presentations lined up, but
Yeah.
We've got a very, I think we've got a good five-minute pitch deck, which I can probably share with you guys, just so you can see kind of how we're positioning the product, the value, how you know, just you know, the initial wedge, everything from kind of...
our consumer thesis to the business model. So I can share the market that we believe we can, you know, take some market share from. So I can share that with you guys probably by the end of the day tomorrow. It's a draft right now that my designer is working on, if that's helpful.
And just kind of piggyback on that, as far as, you know, showing people the game, getting the feedback, the overwhelming response has been, this is amazing, you need less. So there's nothing additionally we would be adding to the scope. It's actually slimming this down and making it a bit more simple for the MVP, foundationally sound. And then
testing. That's the one thing I've just gotten back from everybody is you guys need to test, test, test this and see what people are doing with it, see how people are using it, and go from there. So that'll be the exciting part, learning what people love and building further in that direction. And then product direction, I think the only thing...
time-wise, Matt, would be media and video content. So you might have seen the latest video we had made for the business-to-business product. We love it, and working with that team has been awesome. They are ready to start on one for this version of the product.
They probably begin shooting, what was it, like late September, Matt? And animation would start late Halloween time, early November, for like a mid-November launch so we could have it out before the holidays. So I think there's nothing really on your end other than we would need assets.
Yap.
that they can use, you know, screenshots, you know, some of the raw files, PNGs, things like that, they can start animating.
Okay, that's really helpful to understand, especially like the scope and the testing aspect of it. So I think we're going to have to, and hopefully you've already thought about this, like how are we going to test it in real user groups effectively and gather that feedback. We'll probably have to great plan around that.
All right, maybe from here then I hand it over to Rob for a minute.
Yeah.
Do you want to control the board, Rob, or are you okay just having me sort of park it here?
I took over the screen. Hopefully everybody can see the screen. Okay.
Oh, there we go.
Yes.
I can steal. All right, great. So yeah, so you guys have lots of feedback. I don't know if you guys want to go through and start helping to put that on the stickies. If you already had that consolidated on something where you just, you know, talk to Claude or your Firefly and it just spit out like, here's the actions that need to happen. Because yeah,
Kind of to that point, since I know you guys have been demoing it. Additionally, I can tell because every time I've been logging out and going to the sign up, this has been growing. So I can definitely tell you guys are adding more and more people that made me realize I probably should have added a scrolling feature, but I didn't realize that we'll be using this much. But I'm glad to see everybody's been playing around with it.
Um...
Yeah. So where I was going with that is, yes, so I don't know if you guys have initial feedback right now that you want to start putting on here or if you already have a consolidated deck you want to start sharing. As well as I'd also be curious to start getting the, like I know, Eric, you've been talking about the onboarding flows as well as the, oh, I just got the scribble invitation.
What's A scribble and how do I do it? And those flows to go through that.
So yeah, so let's I guess take some time and yeah, do you have assets you want to share? Do you want to start making?
Comments now.
Yes, for onboarding flows, you know, we're looking at two things. One, a first-time user who just happened to find this product. No invitation. And then similarly, someone who was invited to a wall by a family member, by a friend. I have a flow for that in Figma that I can share with you post this.
It's pretty easy and self-explanatory to go through. But the biggest...
Biggest thing there is really just personalization, like very easy personalization. At every point along the way, reminding the person why they are there, who invited them, and making that feel like they're going to be part of something bigger, as opposed to just a very dry onboarding. So even the opportunity for, say, the inviter to...
pick what the prompt might be or draw a little special invitation or something like that. So happy to share that with you. It's kind of all outlined in that.
Oh, perfect.
Perfect, because yeah, I was thinking about this. What I could do is once you give me those assets, I could rejigger the POC, so then we can always have at least like an initial working copy so we can see it. Then you can obviously then, you know, hey, this is where we're start thinking about, and then the team has something that they can, you know, visualize and.
Queue off of.
As soon as this is done, I'll pull that out of one of my Figma documents and throw it to a fresh one and share that with you.
Beautiful. Awesome. Thank you.
Yap.
Quick question, how do you all share documents internally? Like what works for you? Do you have SharePoint? Do you have some other system? Are you on Google Drive? How do you normally share stuff?
But.
We're on drive for the most part.
OK.
And that's what we've used in the past with our current devs.
Okay, great.
Is Google Drive OK?
We're open to any, we're open to anything though, the one.
thing this team always has issues with is like the Microsoft ecosystem with Teams and all that. I for some reason have like 17 Microsoft accounts since I was like in high school so and it doesn't let me delete any of them. So anything other than the Microsoft ecosystem is probably best for us.
Will do, okay.
Perfect. And then yeah, if you could get me then the list of the changes, which is that I think if you already covered everything in your Figma board, then I might actually just be able to go off of that as well as long as you have all the flows in there. Has Christina had the chance to, because I know she was going to try and make a separate like design feel to this.
you know, version because you have the business to business and now this is the business to client.
Yes.
So I think she's standing by, you know, I was talking to her about this yesterday, to try to understand what the scope of the work would be and how much she's able to commit to it.
Is this as far as, you know, actually designing every screen or a background for every screen? Or is this providing an asset pool that your code takes and kind of populates? And if we need to move that around or fix something that looks to be a bit too much, we can do so. So I guess it's.
How much would you need from her? And what's the best way to go about it?
BU.
Yeah, so I mean...
From what you're telling me, you already have like the Figma flows, which for that really then I just need a couple screens where you've kind of like given the theme. So then I can basically duplicate on the other pages.
So, yeah, so as long as you can give me just just a couple examples, and then, as I said, your full your full wire flame flow, then I can recreate that.
And is there?
Excellent, that's perfect. Is the code base for the current game of any value at all? Because that, I mean, we worked quite a bit on the visuals for that, the one that's, you know, on Zoom. Can you pull from that or is that not helpful?
It is, and I could pull from that if you want me to. It's just, you know, then you're kind of sharing your IP out, so just kind of, you know, alerting you to that. But of course, yes, I could, you know, reuse that, you know, the agents could, you know, steal anything they want from that.
Okay, okay, so then that would live out in the world and we might not want that.
Well, no, no, I mean, you send it to me. It's only on my computer. I'm just telling you that, you know, you're now, you know, sending it over here. That's it. You know, I'm not going to do anything with it. But yeah.
No worries, OK.
As I said, like you could also just, if Christina could just knock out just a couple of like the harder screens with like the theme that she wants, then as I said, I could easily recreate it on the remaining pages, so, or screens.
OK, that's good to know.
So...
Now, I know she very much wants to be involved. What her time availability going forward this fall is going to be is up in the air. But letting her know that, hey, take the screens you want and you think are most important, design the hell out of them, and then we'll work from that. That would be probably the best.
Yeah, because then basically once I get that up and get the app up, then she can come log back in and then be like, oh, well, you missed and should do something here. You should do something here. And I have to acknowledge, dude, she drew one hell of an avatar. Because when I was going through everybody's profiles and I saw this, I was like, whoa, that's good.
Yeah.
Yeah, she's amazing and she's our unofficial gatekeeper when it comes to the branding and the logos and all that. She's been working on it for so long. So I just want to make sure that her fingerprint is on this and that she's happy with it.
Yes, yes. So, and that's the nice thing is then I can turn around, then she can see it, and then we can go back and forth, and then the team hasn't built it out yet, so it's not even like official, and then the team can start building it. So, because the team's obviously going to be a couple weeks behind, obviously, the POC. So.
Excellent.
Go ahead and step over a little bit into this design and core features. Now we're going to kind of go over some more of the same things. So we've already talked about that. We're going to give her the assignment to pick her, you know, most challenging screens, the screens she wants to, you know, really put her touch on. So we'll have Christina start, well, you'll have Christina hopefully start working on that.
So, alright.
Right, you said you're what does the team or team receive the new user flows, depends on. You're going to send me, when can I get the iOS or the Figma flows you were talking about, the Figma designs?
I'll get this up to you by the end of the day, if not sooner.
Military time at.
Working cadence between designer and Rob. So I said, this is one of those things that I don't know if you guys have like a timeline in mind. I feel like we could, you know, maybe set up like maybe a weekly or bi-weekly and then as needed or, you know, she notices that, you know, after I say, hey, the app's been updated, go point out like any issues or things you want updated.
then she just ad hoc sends me items or schedules a meeting. That also works. But is there any like predefined cadence that you would want ahead of time, weekly, bi-weekly?
I think a quick 20, 30 minutes a week just to kind of run through everything, have her give feedback and provide anything right there and then would be best for her.
Oh, do that. And I'll make you, I'll put you on there too. Do you want to be required or optional?
Required.
I'm just thinking. OK, cool.
Not used to be this much typing.
Yeah.
I dictate everything, so this is the most typing you'll ever see me do anymore. Because that's actually what I started doing in meetings so that when I'm talking on mute to the robots, I've just started kind of like going like this so that people can't tell that I'm talking to the robots. So then I don't get the, Rob, you're talking on mute.
You need the two mic set up so you can hit one side to talk to the robots, one side to talk on the call. You just have to remember which is which.
Ohh, there you go, yeah, then I then I would forget which which side is which, but yeah, alright, does new direction change anything we just saw on the app?
What?
It's easy, Rob. Robot's right.
Ha ha ha.
All right, so right, so we already kind of gotten to this point and someone's already fixed this in, right? We need to simplify the flow. I kind of was already like, we kind of knew that. I kind of threw everything at the wall, kind of as we saw. All right, so now let's kind of go through what the core features are and the direction and the shape that we want to go in. So we've kind of like laid down some of these items, but if you see any missing cards,
We can start to add these, but we can start to go through some of these. Oops, it's all this.
Yeah, I think the framing of these are...
We're going to launch in and focus on these first. So this is not that you don't get other stuff. It's that we're trying to maximize the core features up front so that you have something that's like feels whole in each iteration that you get it.
Right, which I feel like I already know, we've already talked about like the onboarding.
We have Auth and onboarding right in the middle.
Okay.
I was gonna...
Because we have onboarding and then what are we calling the other set of flows there, Eric? Because one, as you said, was for New Year's users and one is for the, do we have different invited?
an invited user. Maybe pretty parallel, I think, but what I'll share with you is for an invited user, and then it kind of just gets pared down for a new user.
Okay.
And do we see any cards that are missing? So we got...
Drawing and submit with the submit to unlock.
I don't.
Erica, Eric, how about a card, a card around sharing or generating an artifact, you know, even if it's manual to start, which we can kind of share with you guys some thoughts on that.
Absolutely, yeah.
I think sharing takes 2 paths. Sharing is sharing your individual story. So I created this today. This was my daily prompt. In the same way you might share your Wordle results, you can then share that to various other socials. And then there's that kind of collaborative piece.
Okay.
that I think we would need to get into is how could you choose X amount of drawings off your wall and then manipulate them, whether that is doing it manually yourself, same manner you would do stickers on your phone, spinning them, resizing them, that sort of thing. Or is there, you know, what Bounteous was working on, not Bounteous, I'm sorry, Mission, the...
AI and Claude recognizing the art, pulling the data, and then placing it on a canvas.
which may be a bit further down the road for us.
Okay.
Yeah, so I feel like this, yeah, picking the multiple pictures and grouping them and then doing something more with them might be a little bit like further down here. And then I feel like the sharing personal, though, I feel like that could be closer in here.
Yeah, the things I see here that we were talking through is sort of the gamification side of it to keep engagement up. So that streaks progression, push notifications.
So I feel like sharing is a part of that same theme.
Allegri.
Makes sense.
Eric, is there do we want to touch upon that second card as it relates to the daily prompt and currently the thought of using, you know, Claude because. One of the one of our concerns is that daily prompt.
They're really bizarre. They don't really work for our brand and kind of our vision for this as a social health app, which, you know, I think we probably need to, well, I can let Eric talk to it, but, you know, today we curate.
all those decks and all those prompts on the B2B side of the business with a lot of intention and a lot of meaning. And we think that that is going to be essential, especially during this MVP that the prompts are
always are making people think, people are being thoughtful, and it's not just draw, you know, I don't know, draw your, you know, your favorite pizza or so anyway, that was that as we were demoing this.
Yeah.
That was probably one of the, like, oh, did you guys create this prompt? What is this prompt? This is, this just feels off. This isn't you guys. So just to be thought.
Yeah, there's a time and a place, there's a time and a place for these clawed prompts, and that's within the walls. You know, you had labeled them like the challenges, but when you're playing, you know, ad hoc with your family or your friend group, the ability for you to either write your own prompts or for the game to spin one up for you based on...
Who?
input, such as who's in the group, what other drawings have they done, what have you shared together, what has your response has been? I think that would be better for Claude creating prompts. For the time being, that daily prompt, we need to do it and handle it ourselves. They're surprisingly rigorously gone through.
by our program team who is made-up of mental health professionals, educators, people from all over. And it's kind of, I've learned a lot through the process over the past few years. Asking the simplest question can sometimes be dangerous to certain groups of people. So they have to
They look at it from every angle. They provide it in the safest wording, and it's the most thought-provoking. So we would, I would say, probably create a couple months worth to start of just those daily prompts. We also want to be able to schedule them, you know, holidays, back to school, weather.
anything that could influence that day.
Perfect. That's actually what I did with the POC was Claude generated the prompts, but they're all set to a specific date. And so there was actually like, I think I generated like 3 months in advance just so I had enough in the database for you guys to demo off of. But no, no, that sounds great.
What will be helpful actually is, you know, we could ask, hey, generate us a bunch of prompts for October and then take that as a starting point. Go in and go, okay, we love this concept. We love this idea. Let's expand upon it.
Yeah.
Yeah, we can even help you like create a skill for that too. So then if you have like any form of theming you want to do, you just kind of give the theming and then it'll like, you know, here are the top suggested prompts and like maybe even kicks off agents to like try and validate them like for specific standards and then you know gives that you that output a list. Sorry, go ahead, Marty. Were you going to say something?
Yes, sir.
Awesome.
So from my point of view on this, what you're saying totally makes sense. One of the reasons we had this end here as Claude was finding opportunities to accelerate your ability to manage this. So, you know, we don't want to put an AI hammer on everything that doesn't make sense. So
But we do want to effectively enable you as much as possible to move fast and manage this effectively. And so just that lens of where can we do that? Like, let's look for those opportunities.
Makes sense.
Yeah, I think as a draft, helping us draft these and create those initial, you know, ideas and thoughts for prompts would be incredibly helpful. It's just, you know, our entire modality is based on these prompts and making sure that we have final say and a hand in them. As unfortunately manual as that might be, it's one of the things that sets us apart.
Yap.
Right.
Yeah, I'd also say, and Rob, you may have already done this, but if Eric, if you could feed your current set of curated sets of prompts, then that will help Claude build new ones that kind of fit the model. So you're training it to think like you. I still, I, you know, still have the manual process of.
of double check of, you know, in the creation, but I'd say that plus I think having a curated knowledge base of research around what's effective in these kinds of conversations. I know you work with a lot of groups that do research in this area.
So having that to feed Claude as well, now you're going to get better starting points that you can work from.
So the more you can give Rob to help it think in the way that you think about it, it will help you start off in better places.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Yeah, agents love examples, especially if you can give them like exact examples of what you want. Like you always tell it like, you know, here's the output style that I want, but if you can give it set examples, then it has more to work off of.
So one of the things I pulled up this analytics and instrumentation, I feel like this should be up more in the daily right here, not the next. I feel like, because I know you guys really want to be able to track where they are in the app, because again, this is kind of like what will help you then determine what new features to build out, where we should start paying attention.
So am I right in moving this up into the green or do we want to leave it in the orange?
No, I think that's correct. I'm not sure how deep this should go. We'll obviously maybe lean on you all for some examples of what you've seen in the past. But yes, the ability to track this in real time and even for Matt before he jumps in a meeting to very quickly look at something and gather all the info he needs about the game, you know, number of players, how often they're playing,
Yeah.
Just simple statistics like that, they go a long way when he's meeting with investors and doing demos.
Yeah, and we came up with, we came up, we designed a couple different metrics that I can share with you. They're super simple. We were thinking about it in terms of the MVP, just like things as simple as, you know, can one person bring a close group in to scribble? Does that group come back after the first discovery? Do members invite others?
Do do you have a?
Sorry, go ahead.
to start new groups, number of groups with three plus members where at least 50% contribute in any given week. So we've got kind of a list of things that we think, you know, as we get through, you know, the first 30, 60 days of the beta that will be relevant to investors and, you know, and others alike.
So.
Perfect, perfect. Yeah, give me that list so that then I...
Do you have an do you have an existing platform that you use for your your other apps?
We don't, we don't go ahead, Eric, sir. I was just going to you go, go, go.
So.
I'm glad that I was gonna say it currently.
The.
Currently, all the data that comes from the B2B game goes through metabase and it's parsed there in a very rudimentary.
kind of dashboard. And that's also, that's parts of that dashboard are mirrored within the game itself. So if you go to your account settings as a host, you can see like what your team has been up to, or we can go and see what the game has been up to as a whole. It is again, very rudimentary. It is not intuitive. I can barely process it and run it. So, because I don't know SQL.
So, yeah, we'd like something a bit easier.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, we'll make a nice neat dashboard then.
Awesome.
Beautiful.
All right, so I think we've kind of gone through, are there any other cards in this green one before we go into the orange section? Or is there anything we should add?
Um...
Think so.
I think that's good for the green. We can talk about, then when we get to the orange, I've got a couple things.
Okay. All right. Well, let's go ahead and start talking about the orange.
I don't think I quite got the color matching, but oh well.
Awesome. Was there additional oranges you said you wanted to add? So we got the push notifications, the daily nudge, moderation, streaks, progression, sharing personal.
Yeah, so I was able to.
Which that was the new card.
I don't even know if it would be, actually, it would be a new card and I think it would be.
reactions and comments.
Two other stories.
I was speaking, I spent a lot of time with Steve Roberts, who is an advisor of ours. He's formerly VP of PlayStation. He's a very bright guy when it comes to games, help build up Epic. And so he has a pretty good idea of what he's talking about when it comes to this stuff. And we were talking a lot about the ability to
both moderate and comment on these walls. And he said, you know, why did you pull comments away from? I was like, well, for safety reasons. You know, you have a giant wall that, say, a larger organization has, it could get very quickly out of hand. And he's like, I agree, but a family or a small friend group
Can be more self-regulating, and...
have the ability to moderate themselves. And so we kind of spoke about how we could handle something like that. And in the same way you have, like, say, Google Safe Search, where you've got three settings of, you know, low, medium, high, of how much it's filtering for you. Should we be thinking about...
hosts or owners of walls being able to toggle certain features. So, for instance, small family group, can my mom, the grandmother, leave a comment or speak back to, you know, my nieces, the grandkids?
And I think losing the back and forth there for a small family group.
would be detrimental. But if you say have Patagonia or a celebrity and they have this wall with thousands of users, the ability for people to comment back and forth might get problematic. And they might want to turn that off completely, something that's almost like only outwardly shooting like a...
Letterbox, you know, you go on there, you write your review, somebody can like it, but that's about it. There's no back and forth comments.
Yeah, so does that, I mean, does that make sense?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that makes sense. Sorry, go ahead, David. I wanna go down some.
I, I...
Yeah, I was just gonna say there's a whole roadmap.
of that type of moderation that's going to take a lot of time to work through, right? And how deep do you want to go in monitoring content, stopping content, inappropriate content, sharing, not sharing, like that. There's a lot that gets into. So definitely that needs to be on the roadmap.
I think for phase one or beta, you know, you just need to have a point of view that you write down, stamp it. It's clear in your terms of what you will and won't do. You know, the point of view needs to be there, in other words, and we need to bake it in. And then just know that that's a long road.
Yeah, we talked a lot about moderation with him, and I think that's something that would come later when we start opening this up for those larger groups and those larger walls. And then maybe, you know, just for the MVP, for the time being, just the ability to turn on and off the comment or toggle the ability to comment might just be good enough. And we let it be self-moderating, self-regulating.
I was just thinking about this. We also could finally use Claude for something. We could have where when you submit a comment, it goes through like a Haiku Claude where Haiku like reads it, says, like looks at the wall, like can I post this here? And then like, you know, talks to the user and like won't post unless it could get past a specific like.
AI filter, which that would be on the phone, and that would be like really easy to implement too, while also doing your toggles as well, yeah.
Yeah, I think that would be good.
I just want to mention, because I know we had originally said no comment, and then he kind of sold me on, for these smaller groups, it might be very important.
Yeah.
I think one thing that'll impact.
But then he also said definitely bigger groups. Oh, go ahead.
One thing that for us that will impact this is...
the target user groups and understanding them. So families are different than corporate events sort of thing. And so if both audiences are in play, we need to have a point of view for both of those. And I don't know if that's a toggle for the type of, you know, deployment you're using or whatever, but we need to make sure that we account for those. And if there's other audiences that you're getting into.
Yap.
you know, on the roadmap, it'd be good to understand those two.
Matt, when you share that pitch deck, I think that outlines it pretty well.
Yeah, I did.
Yeah, it definitely, I mean, I mean, I think, listen, for the MVP, I think we are absolutely focused on that, those families and close groups. These are small groups, they're already connected. They have,
have an organizer, they've got strong motivation to use the tool. Yeah, definitely not the corporate play out of the gates, but you'll kind of see kind of how we're thinking about the expansion of the app, right? From small groups to, you know, communities or schools or sports teams or bands, you know, like just, you know, more.
larger groups, but not necessarily family. And then obviously, you know, you have that, the potential to do like brand experience, whether it's partners like Patagonia or whatnot. But we've got a couple examples in the deck that I'll share.
So I split the cards because I feel like reactions are kind of like a, that's a go no matter what. Do we want to put the comments up here in the yellow section or do we want to go in gray on this one? Just out of curiosity, because I mean, I could see this like us adding a lot to make this more complicated or making this simple, but then like that would allow too much through and
I still lean on the side of simple. I think that if we're getting all this feedback, hey, I wish I could comment on my grandkids.
Yap.
scribble or hey, I wish I could comment on my friend's post. That will be good information for us. I think the ability just to share some sentiment via an emoji or reaction is enough for the MVP. Because technically they could listen to your story. I mean, they're going to have the ability to read, to listen to.
Yeah.
I, I...
Eric, I mean, you might have a different point of view, but I I I don't think that's essential for these first 30-60 days as we as we launch this and get, you know, 500 close groups using it.
I would agree, I think.
initial launch we might want to have responses and commenting there, but for the testing I would actually love to see do people want it or not. So leave it down there.
All right, so we're running a little close on time and I really want to get to the next section. So if we just run through this bottom row real quick. So we got the App Store readiness compliance.
release bays, we have the reinvent in the wall. We have our, you know, Copa and the family edition.
The picking up multiple features, and this was, I think, when we split off of from the share personal, which I brought that part up, but as I said, that one was slightly more cumbersome, so I broke that one up right now. And then we obviously have been in the comments right now. Anything else look out of the place here, because other than that, I'm going to pass back to David and we're going to go over to the next section.
Eric, do you want to touch upon really quickly on some of the conversations we've had about speed to monetization?
We do not want this to be a freemium product forever. We want to monetize this as quickly as possible. And we got some really good insight into that. So I don't know if that is part of this gray section, but the ability to monetize this or is that essentially going to be done, you know, within the app stores and or.
You know.
I think we need to take a look at, we need to take a look after this testing phase and see how people are using it and what makes the most sense. You know, granted that testing phase won't be like a general public release, so I think we'd be okay learning and figuring out exactly how we would want to move forward. Talking to Steve some more.
Yeah, I mean, you.
Yap.
and kind of figuring out what features people are leaning on, and you know, are people making 20 walls? And that's okay, now we need to put, you know, the amount of walls behind a paywall or something like that, so.
I would definitely say it belongs in gray.
I would also just plan testing before and after and maybe multiple paywall scenarios because you're going to change user behavior the moment they have to pay for something and you want to monitor what happens. So if you, you know, launch a paid feature and that reduces your use in the app or whatever, you need to know it.
Okay.
Tom.
All right, there's nothing else. Go ahead.
I, so we just on that, we talked about putting the hooks in for.
the monetization side of this. So to me, I think those probably need to be in place for the App Store release side of it, whether or not they're turned on. So I think that's a gray button thing of just having the infrastructure in place that also allows you to potentially test.
Different pace scenarios with different test groups, sort of thing.
That doesn't need to be super complicated, but we need to be able to like have the basics there.
All right, David, I must stop sharing if you want to take over.
Yap.
Okay, so 9 minutes.
What we need to get out of this for next step is get some sort of meeting alignment in place for how we want to work together. So we're going to kick off the first two weeks are very discovery prototype focused to make sure that we align on the features that we were just talking about.
And then we have basically 3 two-week sprints to build stuff out. So that timeline is going to move very fast and we want to be effective with it. So the first thing is we want to be able to do these demos and have handoffs to you. What iteration works for you on that?
We can go on these sort of sprint boundaries or we can make that whatever. And then also what day works best, you know, midweek, Friday, whatever.
Um...
I don't think, I think the day we can, we will make whatever work. I think it's whatever works best for how you're planning out the sprints when you're starting them. If you tell us Friday's the best day, we'll make it Friday and we'll make it work.
Okay, okay. We had a discussion yesterday internally and just aligned on Wednesday as a going in position, just because of the India time zone between teams and it sits midweek to where, you know, it's easier to work with. But that could be Tuesday, Thursday, whatever, just, you know, let me know what schedule.
Works for you guys, and then...
If possible, warnings are best as well, so that the India teams can attend.
Okay, I mean if we want to say Wednesday mornings, if that's what you think works best, let's do it.
OK, great.
Angie.
Yeah, I think also as best practice. I don't know when, when eight weeks is so short, but I think like maybe like a session or two where we're bringing in, obviously assuming that there's no objections from the scribble team, just to bring in like the AE from AWS and be like, hey, this is how we're progressing. Because I always want to make sure that as partners are working and that they're ensuring that.
We're progressing, there's no escalations, makes everything just a ways of working.
Um, next piece is...
readouts and the fidelity of them. We can, you know, we have projects that have readout decks that are like, you know, 10 slides long and very verbose with burndown charts. And we have other clients that just like to move fast, do the demo, and move on. The difference between those things.
Booth.
Oh, is like if you're going to take the readout materials we send you and share it with stakeholders, investors, or whatever, as like, hey, here's what's happening on the project. You know, we want to have some professional fidelity to that if that's the case.
That comes.
Yeah, I think I think the latter. I think move fast, get to the get to the demo. We don't need anything elaborate. We never have.
Okay, fantastic.
I mean, that's why I love to hear it. Just it's more time for the team working on stuff versus prepping for you. Yeah.
Um...
Okay, so we're going to schedule stand-ups on our side. We're going to make them mornings.
Who from your side do you want to be a part of that? Eric, do you want to join those? Do you want to have a cadence with Rob instead or myself or whatever? We can be pretty fluid on that as well. We obviously meet internally no matter what.
You can include me on that as well.
OK.
Okay, so we'll do daily stand-ups, morning time frame. Rob and I will reach out to the team and propose a couple of blocks.
Um...
Let's see, the other thing is AWS environments. So do you have anything stood up? Do you need us to do that?
Do we have maybe this is Angie question too, like are the reps providing anything as a part of the funding? We just want to make sure that we're moving quick on the right environment structure.
I think a lot of it would be, that's the reason why I'm like, let's just so be nice and include them so that when we need, hey, by the way, we need this is an easy ask. So you tell me when it makes sense.
to bring them in, right? And then also if there is a list of asks that we want from them.
Let's put that out.
Okay.
And then if you all could share anything you have on this list, so if you already have, you know, company account for Android, Apple, you know, AWS, whatever, then the sooner we get access to that stuff, the better. We can obviously move with our own accounts in the meantime.
I'll actually, I've got a message going over to James post this, so I will screenshot this and see what he might have for us for that. I can tell you right off the bat, we probably don't have Apple or Google Play accounts.
Okay.
All right, so down here.
We want to schedule some of these initial kickoffs right away. So I think we digest if you could send us over or.
create a session to work with us to hand over what materials you have, like all of that feedback. Let's get that session together. And I think that will feed directly into prioritization coming out of that. So that's probably a first order of business to get on the calendar.
Team orientation, product deep dive. This is an internal thing that we're doing. This is happening this week. We're also going to do a ways of working. Are you guys cool with using JIRA?
Yap.
Um, okay.
So we'll put together the boards, the architecture docs, all that stuff, and we'll get that shared over to you and provide access as well so that everybody will just be in the same space.
Okay.
Rob, can you think of anything we're missing?
To get things moving.
No, I mean, I don't think though. I think we have, you know, basically the sooner you can get me the artifacts, I can get the POC updated, which is, you know, just that much easier. But yeah.
Do you guys have a repository you guys want us to use or do you guys just want us to use Bounteous for right now and then later on we can migrate the code into your own repository?
And probably the latter.
Okay.
Right.
Awesome. All right. So to do on our side is we're going to have an internal sync and then give you some time slots for upcoming meetings this week and next week.
Awesome.
Excellent.
And I'll shoot you those Figma files should be by end of day.
Perfect. Thank you.
Cool. Oh, one more thing. I'm headed out. Look at that. Marty's Marty's showing off. I love it.
I forgot, I forgot to properly attire for this call.
The.
Yap.
Awesome.
I did, so David, I did wear this for you. I won't show the logo.
Oh, geez.
I love it. I love it. I switched. I was wearing that earlier today and I wanted to look like a little bit more professional for the call. So there you go.
Yeah, I appreciate that. Thanks for calling me out there.
I feel like I need to have a little T-shirt. Go ahead.
Hey, I'm wearing running clothes.
Oh, excellent.
Get us, get us those mailing addresses, you know, we'll get you guys some care packages.
Yeah.
I was gonna say, I want a hat.
More than just hats, Rob. We got you.
OK, awesome.
Also, heads up, I'm out for the next two weeks. I'm headed on a Baltic vacation. So if you're in good hands with Rob and John, and then, you know, I'll catch you on the other side of the first two week phase.
Awesome. Enjoy.
Are you trip?
Yeah, have a great trip.
Yeah, I'm excited.
I want to just keep having clots on your emails, David.
Haha.
Ha ha.
I'm going to have Claude respond right back to you. It's totally fine.
Ping you.
Perfect.
All right, guys. Thank you very much. We appreciate it. Yeah, thank you. Appreciate it.
Thanks, team.
Right. Thank you all.
Thank you.
Take care.